Narrator: 1
Speaker: I arrived in Paris on Friday night.
Narrator: 2
Speaker: I was very tired when I arrived at the hotel.
Narrator: 3
Speaker: I hate waiting for people who are late.
Narrator: 4
Speaker A: What are you going to do at the weekend?
Speaker B: I don’t know. It depends on the weather.
Narrator: 5
Speaker: I’m sorry, but I really don’t agree with you.
Narrator: 6
Speaker: I asked for a chicken sandwich, but this is tuna!
Narrator: 7
Speaker: Please listen to what I’m saying!
Narrator: 8
Speaker: Who’s going to pay for the meal?
Narrator: 9
Speaker: I need to speak to Martin about the meeting.
Narrator: 10
Speaker: I don’t spend much money on food.
Narrator: 11
Speaker: Don’t worry about the exam.
It isn’t very hard.
Narrator: 12
Speaker: Do you believe in ghosts?
Narrator: 13
Speaker: You’re not listening!
What are you thinking about?
Narrator: 14
Speaker A: What do you think of this painting?
Speaker B: I really like it.
I think it’s beautiful.
Narrator: 15
Speaker: Who does this bag belong to?